[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like this?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "seen", "anything", "quite", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "You know, usually when they lie, they sort of hedge it and they dissemble and they find an element that maybe you can quibble over, you know, what that word really meant or what it didn't mean, but he flat-out lied.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "usually", "when", "they", "lie", ",", "they", "sort", "of", "hedge", "it", "and", "they", "dissemble", "and", "they", "find", "an", "element", "that", "maybe", "you", "can", "quibble", "over", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "that", "word", "really", "meant", "or", "what", "it", "did", "n't", "mean", ",", "but", "he", "flat-out", "lied", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Why hasn't he resigned?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "n't", "he", "resigned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "He thinks probably he can survive this, if he comes, you know, opens up about it and goes into some sort of therapy, says he's going to have some therapy.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "thinks", "probably", "he", "can", "survive", "this", ",", "if", "he", "comes", ",", "you", "know", ",", "opens", "up", "about", "it", "and", "goes", "into", "some", "sort", "of", "therapy", ",", "says", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "have", "some", "therapy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "He doesn't know, does he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "know", ",", "does", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I don't know if he knows or if he doesn't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "he", "knows", "or", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "That would become a criminal matter?", "question_tokens": ["That", "would", "become", "a", "criminal", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "It might be.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "might", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "And flying ever high, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "flying", "ever", "high", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "And, you know, he was on a path to becoming the next mayor of New York City if he would have played his cards right.", "answer_tokens": ["And", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "was", "on", "a", "path", "to", "becoming", "the", "next", "mayor", "of", "New", "York", "City", "if", "he", "would", "have", "played", "his", "cards", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "I mean, is that dream over for him now?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "that", "dream", "over", "for", "him", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Probably.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Will the lying be more problematic than the original crime?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "the", "lying", "be", "more", "problematic", "than", "the", "original", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBG", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "It's one of these situations where you're caught so blatantly lying.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "one", "of", "these", "situations", "where", "you", "'re", "caught", "so", "blatantly", "lying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Can anybody believe you again?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "anybody", "believe", "you", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, watching that clip of you and him, he was so credible, really.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "watching", "that", "clip", "of", "you", "and", "him", ",", "he", "was", "so", "credible", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton", "Monica Lewinsky"], "LOCATION": ["Roosevelt Room"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "In all your time, Wolf, at CNN, have you ever had anyone in political life, with reasonably high office, look you in the eye and lie like Anthony Weiner did?", "question_tokens": ["In", "all", "your", "time", ",", "Wolf", ",", "at", "CNN", ",", "have", "you", "ever", "had", "anyone", "in", "political", "life", ",", "with", "reasonably", "high", "office", ",", "look", "you", "in", "the", "eye", "and", "lie", "like", "Anthony", "Weiner", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, I was in the Roosevelt Room when Bill Clinton was accused of the Monica Lewinsky.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "in", "the", "Roosevelt", "Room", "when", "Bill", "Clinton", "was", "accused", "of", "the", "Monica", "Lewinsky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "PERSON": ["Wolf", "Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "JJS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Are you the barometer for them lying?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "the", "barometer", "for", "them", "lying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "In all my years, and most always, you know, there are plenty of liars out there, but they tell the truth, and if they're going to -- they don't blatantly lie as Anthony Weiner did, so specifically.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "all", "my", "years", ",", "and", "most", "always", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "are", "plenty", "of", "liars", "out", "there", ",", "but", "they", "tell", "the", "truth", ",", "and", "if", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "--", "they", "do", "n't", "blatantly", "lie", "as", "Anthony", "Weiner", "did", ",", "so", "specifically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJS", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Do you actually believe that it is material to a man's fitness to preside in high office in American politics as to how he conducts himself in his private life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "actually", "believe", "that", "it", "is", "material", "to", "a", "man", "'s", "fitness", "to", "preside", "in", "high", "office", "in", "American", "politics", "as", "to", "how", "he", "conducts", "himself", "in", "his", "private", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "I think to most Americans, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "to", "most", "Americans", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Are you a betting man?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "betting", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "If you were, how long would you give him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", ",", "how", "long", "would", "you", "give", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Have you ever drunk alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "drunk", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "You don't -- you've never taken drugs?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "--", "you", "'ve", "never", "taken", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "And presumably, we never -- you never had an affair, because you couldn't have done it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "presumably", ",", "we", "never", "--", "you", "never", "had", "an", "affair", ",", "because", "you", "could", "n't", "have", "done", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "And you can say that with total non-Schwarzenegger certainty?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "can", "say", "that", "with", "total", "non-Schwarzenegger", "certainty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "JJR", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "So this is a -- I would say this is one of your trump cards, because when you look at all these politicians at the moment, whether it's Anthony Weiner or it's John Edwards or it's Arnold Schwarzenegger, the one thing we don't have to worry about in America if you're elected president is anything tumbling out of the -- the cupboard, right, Ann?", "question_tokens": ["So", "this", "is", "a", "--", "I", "would", "say", "this", "is", "one", "of", "your", "trump", "cards", ",", "because", "when", "you", "look", "at", "all", "these", "politicians", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "whether", "it", "'s", "Anthony", "Weiner", "or", "it", "'s", "John", "Edwards", "or", "it", "'s", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", ",", "the", "one", "thing", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "worry", "about", "in", "America", "if", "you", "'re", "elected", "president", "is", "anything", "tumbling", "out", "of", "the", "--", "the", "cupboard", ",", "right", ",", "Ann", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "It better not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "better", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner", "John Edwards", "Arnold Schwarzenegger", "Ann"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Michael Sitrick, on a scale of one to 10, just how tarnished is Anthony Weiner's reputation right now?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", "Sitrick", ",", "on", "a", "scale", "of", "one", "to", "10", ",", "just", "how", "tarnished", "is", "Anthony", "Weiner", "'s", "reputation", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", ",", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Probably eight.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "eight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Sitrick", "Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Is it retrievable?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "retrievable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "I think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "And one of them was Anthony Weiner, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "one", "of", "them", "was", "Anthony", "Weiner", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What does he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "So, he sits down.", "answer_tokens": ["So", ",", "he", "sits", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vicky"], "LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Let's make one thing clear, he was single at the time, but did lie to you about what his occupation was?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "make", "one", "thing", "clear", ",", "he", "was", "single", "at", "the", "time", ",", "but", "did", "lie", "to", "you", "about", "what", "his", "occupation", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "And he opened the conversation with a lie, at which point I replied, I'm Vicky from England, because, you know, if he wants to play chess, I'll play chess, too.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "he", "opened", "the", "conversation", "with", "a", "lie", ",", "at", "which", "point", "I", "replied", ",", "I", "'m", "Vicky", "from", "England", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "he", "wants", "to", "play", "chess", ",", "I", "'ll", "play", "chess", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "How would you describe this new era of Facebook/Twitter infidelity?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "this", "new", "era", "of", "Facebook/Twitter", "infidelity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "You know, I think what it does is it provides a forum, a platform, if you like, for people's ability or, you know, voluntary sort of deep insecurities.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "what", "it", "does", "is", "it", "provides", "a", "forum", ",", "a", "platform", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "for", "people", "'s", "ability", "or", ",", "you", "know", ",", "voluntary", "sort", "of", "deep", "insecurities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Because he says he didn't have any physical contact with these women?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "he", "says", "he", "did", "n't", "have", "any", "physical", "contact", "with", "these", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "That's a real tough one.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "real", "tough", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 238, "question": "What's your answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "You know, I think they're morally both pretty --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "morally", "both", "pretty", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "But is it easy to stand by your mind if in your head and heart you know he wasn't physically unfaithful?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "easy", "to", "stand", "by", "your", "mind", "if", "in", "your", "head", "and", "heart", "you", "know", "he", "was", "n't", "physically", "unfaithful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "No, because in his mind, he was.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "in", "his", "mind", ",", "he", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "And what is he doing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "he", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "The same thing to you.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "same", "thing", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Weiner"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "From a male point of view, what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["From", "a", "male", "point", "of", "view", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Look, I think that -- I think that Weiner felt that he wasn't cheating, that this was -- you know, look, one of the problems with e-mail is people say things in e-mail, thinking that they're not going to be discovered.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "that", "--", "I", "think", "that", "Weiner", "felt", "that", "he", "was", "n't", "cheating", ",", "that", "this", "was", "--", "you", "know", ",", "look", ",", "one", "of", "the", "problems", "with", "e-mail", "is", "people", "say", "things", "in", "e-mail", ",", "thinking", "that", "they", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "be", "discovered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Would you seek professional help?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "seek", "professional", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "I have not -- you know, I'm going to try to handle this and I haven't ruled out perhaps seeing someone, but I'm not blaming anyone.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "not", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "try", "to", "handle", "this", "and", "I", "have", "n't", "ruled", "out", "perhaps", "seeing", "someone", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "not", "blaming", "anyone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Why would he do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "he", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, this is the question everyone shakes their head and ask, when they look at young men of any age behaving such as this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "the", "question", "everyone", "shakes", "their", "head", "and", "ask", ",", "when", "they", "look", "at", "young", "men", "of", "any", "age", "behaving", "such", "as", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Is it as serious, do you think, as physical infidelity?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "as", "serious", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "as", "physical", "infidelity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, it's interesting that men and women tend to experience this somewhat differently.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "that", "men", "and", "women", "tend", "to", "experience", "this", "somewhat", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Is this a deliberate strategy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "a", "deliberate", "strategy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Well, I stopped wearing my suit to be at night.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "stopped", "wearing", "my", "suit", "to", "be", "at", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "You have a whole team of people that analyze and debate whether you should wear a tie or not, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "a", "whole", "team", "of", "people", "that", "analyze", "and", "debate", "whether", "you", "should", "wear", "a", "tie", "or", "not", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "No, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "This is politics, you know?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "politics", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Who of all these names do you see as a serious contender at this stage?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "of", "all", "these", "names", "do", "you", "see", "as", "a", "serious", "contender", "at", "this", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, they're all serious contenders.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "all", "serious", "contenders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Is there a smoldering volcano?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "smoldering", "volcano", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I have --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "-- that we don't know about?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I have Romney genes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "Romney", "genes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "I mean, do you honestly believe that a Republican president would have got America out of that hole any faster?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "honestly", "believe", "that", "a", "Republican", "president", "would", "have", "got", "America", "out", "of", "that", "hole", "any", "faster", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "-- how is it that America under eight years of the Republicans got themselves into the biggest hole of all time?", "question_tokens": ["--", "how", "is", "it", "that", "America", "under", "eight", "years", "of", "the", "Republicans", "got", "themselves", "into", "the", "biggest", "hole", "of", "all", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Well, I'm not going to speak about all Republicans.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "speak", "about", "all", "Republicans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "So you would actively distance yourself from the whole Bush years?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "actively", "distance", "yourself", "from", "the", "whole", "Bush", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, a number -- look, a number of the things President Bush did were absolutely right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "number", "--", "look", ",", "a", "number", "of", "the", "things", "President", "Bush", "did", "were", "absolutely", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "This is, it seems to me, your Achilles' heel, the one where you're in most trouble, because when the president, who is a Democrat, starts praising you for your health care plan, that's not good, is it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "me", ",", "your", "Achilles", "'", "heel", ",", "the", "one", "where", "you", "'re", "in", "most", "trouble", ",", "because", "when", "the", "president", ",", "who", "is", "a", "Democrat", ",", "starts", "praising", "you", "for", "your", "health", "care", "plan", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "good", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "JJ", ",", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, I think the president is hoping that we'll be diverted from the fact that ObamaCare is going to get repealed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "president", "is", "hoping", "that", "we", "'ll", "be", "diverted", "from", "the", "fact", "that", "ObamaCare", "is", "going", "to", "get", "repealed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ":", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "But isn't the idea the same?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "n't", "the", "idea", "the", "same", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "OMNEY: Let's come -- let's come back.", "answer_tokens": ["OMNEY", ":", "Let", "'s", "come", "--", "let", "'s", "come", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Isn't the idea the same?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "the", "idea", "the", "same", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "You know, the -- if you say the idea is the same, you've got a 2,700 page bill.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "--", "if", "you", "say", "the", "idea", "is", "the", "same", ",", "you", "'ve", "got", "a", "2,700", "page", "bill", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "-- they've got to support?", "question_tokens": ["--", "they", "'ve", "got", "to", "support", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Well, the great news is that when I finally debate President Obama, it will be wonderful, because he won't be able to say I'm some heartless Republican that doesn't care about people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "great", "news", "is", "that", "when", "I", "finally", "debate", "President", "Obama", ",", "it", "will", "be", "wonderful", ",", "because", "he", "wo", "n't", "be", "able", "to", "say", "I", "'m", "some", "heartless", "Republican", "that", "does", "n't", "care", "about", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Do you have any?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "-- I -- I point out that there are a number of things in the bill I didn't like, the parts I vetoed.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "--", "I", "point", "out", "that", "there", "are", "a", "number", "of", "things", "in", "the", "bill", "I", "did", "n't", "like", ",", "the", "parts", "I", "vetoed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Do you regret it in the way it played out?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "it", "in", "the", "way", "it", "played", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "But let me tell you this, which is I know that a lot of people who say my political prospects would be much, much better if I were just to say oh, it was just a mistake, it was a bone-headed idea, I'm so sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "let", "me", "tell", "you", "this", ",", "which", "is", "I", "know", "that", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "who", "say", "my", "political", "prospects", "would", "be", "much", ",", "much", "better", "if", "I", "were", "just", "to", "say", "oh", ",", "it", "was", "just", "a", "mistake", ",", "it", "was", "a", "bone-headed", "idea", ",", "I", "'m", "so", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Has it worked in Massachusetts?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "worked", "in", "Massachusetts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "You know, that's really up to the people of Massachusetts.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "really", "up", "to", "the", "people", "of", "Massachusetts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Yes, but has it worked?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "has", "it", "worked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, it's up to the people of Massachusetts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "up", "to", "the", "people", "of", "Massachusetts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Has it worked?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "worked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "The answer is yes.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "answer", "is", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Has it cost more money each year to implement RomneyCare?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "cost", "more", "money", "each", "year", "to", "implement", "RomneyCare", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Well, it's about -- I understand it's about one percent of the state budget.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "about", "--", "I", "understand", "it", "'s", "about", "one", "percent", "of", "the", "state", "budget", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "But in terms of the ideology, are Republicans who say that it's wrong to take those who can't afford the insurance, to mandate them into getting some form of insurance, are they wrong?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "ideology", ",", "are", "Republicans", "who", "say", "that", "it", "'s", "wrong", "to", "take", "those", "who", "ca", "n't", "afford", "the", "insurance", ",", "to", "mandate", "them", "into", "getting", "some", "form", "of", "insurance", ",", "are", "they", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "You said a couple of things there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "said", "a", "couple", "of", "things", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Let me ask you then, do you personally think homosexuality is a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "then", ",", "do", "you", "personally", "think", "homosexuality", "is", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Nice try.", "answer_tokens": ["Nice", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", ":", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Nice try on what?", "question_tokens": ["Nice", "try", "on", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I'm going to tell you that as a leader of the American people, I will do everything in my power to treat all people with respect and dignity, and to -- and to advance the rights people have to choose their own course in life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "that", "as", "a", "leader", "of", "the", "American", "people", ",", "I", "will", "do", "everything", "in", "my", "power", "to", "treat", "all", "people", "with", "respect", "and", "dignity", ",", "and", "to", "--", "and", "to", "advance", "the", "rights", "people", "have", "to", "choose", "their", "own", "course", "in", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]